<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ArcadiusMC</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on ArcadiusMC</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:41:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Server Team</title><link>/wiki/team/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/wiki/team/</guid><description>Open positions If you are interested in joining the staff team, we could use help in the following areas:
Coding: helping with the server&amp;rsquo;s custom plugins. Artist: creating server logo variants, PlanetMC server banner, server texture packs, in-game cosmetics, webstore art, collector cards, and so on. Writer: helping to write the player wiki on complex features such as dungeons, factions, custom items, and so on. Server promotion: bringing more attention to the server, for example through Youtube, Twitch or TikTok.</description></item><item><title>History</title><link>/wiki/history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/wiki/history/</guid><description>ArcadiusMC was created by JulieWoolie, Oweeennnnn and Robinoh in early January of 2024.
The server&amp;rsquo;s first open beta was launched on the 19th of April 2024</description></item><item><title>Punishments</title><link>/adminwiki/punishing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/adminwiki/punishing/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Contributing</title><link>/wiki/contributing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/wiki/contributing/</guid><description>Anyone who wishes to contribute to this wiki can do so by submitting a pull request to the site&amp;rsquo;s GitHub repository here!.
We will review each contribution to ensure the information is correct and doesn&amp;rsquo;t contain any offensive content.</description></item><item><title>Additional Resources</title><link>/adminwiki/morereading/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/adminwiki/morereading/</guid><description>List of additional resources for the plugins/tools we use. WorldEdit Documentation WorldEdit Brushes WorldEdit Patterns WorldGuard Documentation WorldGuard Flags JavaScript docs (For Scripting) Block Display Studio McStacker (For making commands) BlockBench (For Texture Pack) minecraft.tools Minecraft Wiki</description></item><item><title>Arcadius Beta!</title><link>/news/beta/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:41:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/news/beta/</guid><description>Server beta announcement</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>h1 Heading &amp;#x1f60a; h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading Horizontal Rules Typographic replacements Enable typographer option to see result.
(c) (C) (r) (R) (tm) (TM) (p) (P) +-
test.. test&amp;hellip; test&amp;hellip;.. test?&amp;hellip;.. test!&amp;hellip;.
!!!!!! ???? ,, &amp;ndash; &amp;mdash;
&amp;ldquo;Smartypants, double quotes&amp;rdquo; and &amp;lsquo;single quotes&amp;rsquo;
Emphasis This is bold text
This is bold text
This is italic text
This is italic text
Strikethrough
Blockquotes Blockquotes can also be nested&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Prose</title><link>/prose/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>/prose/</guid><description>@tailwindcss/typography View on GitHub!
Beautiful typographic defaults for HTML you don&amp;rsquo;t control.
The official Tailwind CSS Typography plugin provides a set of prose classes you can use to add beautiful typographic defaults to any vanilla HTML you don’t control, like HTML rendered from Markdown, or pulled from a CMS.
Tailwind CSS IntelliSense extension for Visual Studio Code
&amp;lt;article class=&amp;#34;prose lg:prose-xl&amp;#34;&amp;gt; {{ markdown }} &amp;lt;/article&amp;gt; To see what it looks like in action, check out our live demo on Tailwind Play.</description></item><item><title>Block Usables</title><link>/adminwiki/usables/blocks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/adminwiki/usables/blocks/</guid><description>Block usables are usables attached to block entities, they are triggered when you right click the block in question. Other interactions such as breaking, damaging or walking over a block (in the case of pressure plates) are not supported.
Creating a usable block To create a usable block you simply have to add an action or condition to a specified block.
For this example, we&amp;rsquo;ll add a simple show_text action to a chest that&amp;rsquo;ll tell a player &amp;ldquo;Hello, &amp;lt;player name&amp;gt;!</description></item><item><title>Command Search</title><link>/commands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/commands/</guid><description> Search Show Admin commands Show command metadata</description></item><item><title>Events</title><link>/adminwiki/scripts/events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/adminwiki/scripts/events/</guid><description>Examples The following are various examples of how the events object can be used
Simple event registration // Declare the Java type import JoinEvent from &amp;#34;org.bukkit.event.player.PlayerJoinEvent&amp;#34; // Register a function to list to the given event events.register(JoinEvent, onPlayerJoin); // Function called when event is triggered function onPlayerJoin(event) { logger.info(&amp;#34;Player {} joined the server!&amp;#34;, event.player.getName()); } Prioritized listener registration Please see The Bukkit Wiki for information about EventPriority.
// Register a function to list to the given event with the LOWEST // priority events.</description></item><item><title>Frequently asked questions</title><link>/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/faq/</guid><description>🔹 Are there any rules? Yes, there are some major rules. You can do /rules ingame.
🔹 How do I start? Doing /wild will teleport you to a random location on the map. You may use this as many times as you want until you find your optimal location. But the command only works in Hazelguard.
🔹 What is Hazelguard? Hazelguard is the spawn region. It is controlled by the administrator(s), where most major events will occur.</description></item><item><title>Task Scheduling</title><link>/adminwiki/scripts/tasks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/adminwiki/scripts/tasks/</guid><description>ArcadiusMC&amp;rsquo;s scripting abstractions allow for the scheduling of delayed and repeating tasks. All tasks that can be scheduled will be executed on the main thread.
Examples All intervals passed to the scheduler are measured in ticks.
Scheduling a delayed task scheduler.runLater(10 /* Delay in ticks */, task =&amp;gt; { // Perform some action }); Scheduling a repeating task scheduler.runTimer(10 /* Initial Delay */, 10 /* Repeating delay*/, task =&amp;gt; { }); Scheduling a task that only runs n number of times const MAX_RUNS = 20; var runCount = 0; scheduler.</description></item></channel></rss>