<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Player Wiki on ArcadiusMC</title><link>/wiki/</link><description>Recent content in Player Wiki on ArcadiusMC</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/wiki/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Server Team</title><link>/wiki/team/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/wiki/team/</guid><description>Open positions If you are interested in joining the staff team, we could use help in the following areas:
Coding: helping with the server&amp;rsquo;s custom plugins. Artist: creating server logo variants, PlanetMC server banner, server texture packs, in-game cosmetics, webstore art, collector cards, and so on. Writer: helping to write the player wiki on complex features such as dungeons, factions, custom items, and so on. Server promotion: bringing more attention to the server, for example through Youtube, Twitch or TikTok.</description></item><item><title>Regular Resets</title><link>/wiki/resets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/wiki/resets/</guid><description>ArcadiusMC will be regularly reset roughly every 8 months. The world is completely reset, all player data is wiped and reset back to 0.
Players are allowed to keep any items of sentimental value (Trinkets, cards, some items) and bring them with them into the next world. This happens close to the reset where players will be asked to submit their items (in shulkers) to be kept after the reset.</description></item><item><title>Succession Events</title><link>/wiki/succession-events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/wiki/succession-events/</guid><description>Events Succession Events are monthly events in which players compete for the title.
These events happen each month, and are always different. The same skills that may help you win an event, may hinder you in the next.
After winning, an is crowned in the palace at Latium, where they&amp;rsquo;re given their title, the Emperor&amp;rsquo;s Wreath, a special wearable item that players keep forever.
Benefits As emperor, you can give your friends&amp;rsquo; player shops tax or rent exemptions, and punish your foes&amp;rsquo; player shops with tax and rent increases.</description></item><item><title>History</title><link>/wiki/history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/wiki/history/</guid><description>ArcadiusMC was created by JulieWoolie, Oweeennnnn and Robinoh in early January of 2024.
The server&amp;rsquo;s first open beta was launched on the 19th of April 2024</description></item><item><title>Land Claiming</title><link>/wiki/claims/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/wiki/claims/</guid><description>Players on ArcadiusMC can claim land using any golden shovel, and check for claims using any ole&amp;rsquo; stick. But you can get these tools with /kit claim as well.
Creating claims To create a claim, use the Claim Shovel and Right-Click at two points that will outline your claim.
To resize any of your claims, Right-Click with the Claim Shovel on a corner of an existing claim.</description></item><item><title>Contributing</title><link>/wiki/contributing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/wiki/contributing/</guid><description>Anyone who wishes to contribute to this wiki can do so by submitting a pull request to the site&amp;rsquo;s GitHub repository here!.
We will review each contribution to ensure the information is correct and doesn&amp;rsquo;t contain any offensive content.</description></item></channel></rss>